♪Eager to change the planet's orbit♪
حريصة على تغيير مدار الكوكب
♪Unexpectedly, you've become the planned orbit♪
♪ بشكل غير متوقع ، لقد أصبحت المدار المخطط
♪I can't avoid the end designated by you♪
♪ لا أستطيع تجنب النهاية التي حددتها لك ♪
♪Yet you're nowhere to be seen♪
♪ ومع ذلك لا يمكنك رؤيتك في أي مكان
♪I'm determined to look for your trace♪
♪ أنا مصمم على البحث عن أثرك ♪
♪At last, I turned into an unknown star♪
♪ أخيرًا تحولت إلى نجم غير معروف
♪Wandering silently on the edge of the Milky Way♪
♪ تتجول بصمت على حافة درب التبانة
♪Still, I can't see you♪
♪ ما زلت لا أستطيع رؤيتك
♪How to get rid of your gravity♪
♪ كيف تتخلص من جاذبيتك ♪
♪I'm both fascinated and suffocated♪
♪ أنا مفتون ومختنق على حد سواء
♪The cycle is disturbed and the flight is out of control♪
الدورة مضطربة والرحلة خارجة عن السيطرة
♪Eager to crash on the earth with a shooting star♪
♪ حريصة على الاصطدام على الأرض مع شهاب
♪How to counteract your gravity♪
♪ كيفية مواجهة جاذبيتك ♪
♪Pull away from each dimension♪
ابتعد عن كل بُعد ♪
♪Forget everything before I sink♪
♪ انسى كل شيء قبل أن أغرق
♪Even though I don't know my own whereabouts♪
♪ على الرغم من أنني لا أعرف مكاني ♪
=Yan Zhi's Romantic Story=
= قصة رومانسية يان تشي =
=Episode 20=
= الحلقة 20 =
Not available!
غير متوفر!
Yan Ning and Shen Zhizhou announced officially!
أعلن يان نينغ وشين تشيتشو رسميا!
This is the first time
هذه اول مرة
I've ever admired Yan Ning.
لقد أعجبت يان نينغ من أي وقت مضى.
(Comments) (My shrine of adoration is shattered.)
(تعليقات) (تحطم مزار عبادتي.)
- I feel sorry for Gu Han, purr. - Witnessing a moment in history.
- أشعر بالأسف على قو هان ، خرخرة.  - تشهد لحظة في التاريخ.
(Surprise! The female guest and the director got together.)
(مفاجأة! اجتمعت الضيفة والمخرج).
(Yan Ning slept over at Shen Zhizhou's and they went to work together.)
(نام يان نينغ في Shen Zhizhou وذهبوا للعمل معًا).
(Was their love affair true?)
(هل كانت علاقة حبهما حقيقية؟)
(What on earth is going on?)
(ما الذي يحدث على وجه الأرض؟)
What's wrong?
ماالخطب؟
Switch it off,
أطفئه،
or it will be ringing off the hook.
أو سوف يرن من الخطاف.
Wait.
انتظر.
Forward.
إلى الأمام.
OK. Power off.
نعم.  انقطاع التيار الكهربائي.
Feng.
فنغ.
You finally came.
لقد أتيت أخيرًا.
I didn't think I would sit on pins and needles someday.
لم أكن أعتقد أنني سأجلس على دبابيس وإبر يومًا ما.
Feng, I'm sorry.
Feng ، أنا آسف.
I'm sorry to put you in trouble.
أنا آسف لوضعك في مشكلة.
You should worry about yourself.
يجب أن تقلق على نفسك.
You're deep in controversy.
أنت عميق في الجدل.
There are various comments.
هناك العديد من التعليقات.
Your concert has been canceled for good.
تم إلغاء حفلتك الموسيقية إلى الأبد.
You can't release the new album for now.
لا يمكنك إصدار الألبوم الجديد في الوقت الحالي.
Don't worry. As long as I like music,
لا تقلق.  طالما أحب الموسيقى ،
I can sing everywhere.
يمكنني الغناء في كل مكان.
You're right.
أنت على حق.
Yan Ning,
يان نينج ،
I'm going to give you a special concert.
سأقدم لكم حفلة موسيقية خاصة.
this is an online live concert.
هذا حفل موسيقي مباشر عبر الإنترنت.
You can sing whatever you want.
يمكنك أن تغني ما تريد.
The whole world can hear your voice.
يمكن للعالم كله سماع صوتك.
Hello, everyone.
أهلا بالجميع.
Welcome to my concert.
مرحبا بكم في حفلتي الموسيقية.
I'm Yan Ning, a singer.
أنا يان نينغ ، مغنية.
I know these days,
أعرف هذه الأيام ،
Shen Zhizhou and I have many critics.
شين تشيتشو ولدي العديد من النقاد.
I hope you can allow me to sing a song
آمل أن تسمح لي بغناء أغنية
to tell you our story.
لأخبرك قصتنا.
♪Eager to change the planet's orbit♪
حريصة على تغيير مدار الكوكب
♪Unexpectedly, you've become the planned orbit♪
♪ بشكل غير متوقع ، لقد أصبحت المدار المخطط
♪I can't avoid the end designated by you♪
♪ لا أستطيع تجنب النهاية التي حددتها لك ♪
♪Yet you're nowhere to be seen♪
♪ ومع ذلك لا يمكنك رؤيتك في أي مكان
♪I'm determined to look for your trace♪
♪ أنا مصمم على البحث عن أثرك ♪
♪At last, I turned into an unknown star♪
♪ أخيرًا تحولت إلى نجم غير معروف
♪Wandering silently on the edge of the Milky Way♪
♪ تتجول بصمت على حافة درب التبانة
♪Still, I can't see you♪
♪ ما زلت لا أستطيع رؤيتك
♪How to get rid of your gravity♪
♪ كيف تتخلص من جاذبيتك ♪
♪I'm both fascinated and suffocated♪
♪ أنا مفتون ومختنق على حد سواء
♪The cycle is disturbed and the flight is out of control♪
الدورة مضطربة والرحلة خارجة عن السيطرة
♪Eager to crash on the earth with a shooting star♪
♪ حريصة على الاصطدام على الأرض مع شهاب
♪How to counteract your gravity♪
♪ كيفية مواجهة جاذبيتك ♪
♪Pull away from each dimension♪
ابتعد عن كل بُعد ♪
♪Forget everything before I sink♪
♪ انسى كل شيء قبل أن أغرق
♪Even though I don't know my own whereabouts♪
♪ على الرغم من أنني لا أعرف مكاني ♪
♪I'm determined to look for your trace♪
♪ أنا مصمم على البحث عن أثرك ♪
♪At last, I turned into an unknown star♪
♪ أخيرًا تحولت إلى نجم غير معروف
♪Wandering silently on the edge of the Milky Way♪
♪ تتجول بصمت على حافة درب التبانة
♪Still, I can't see you♪
♪ ما زلت لا أستطيع رؤيتك
♪How to get rid of your gravity♪
♪ كيف تتخلص من جاذبيتك ♪
♪I'm both fascinated and suffocated♪
♪ أنا مفتون ومختنق على حد سواء
♪The cycle is disturbed and the flight is out of control♪
الدورة مضطربة والرحلة خارجة عن السيطرة
♪Eager to crash on the earth with a shooting star♪
♪ حريصة على الاصطدام على الأرض مع شهاب
♪How to counteract your gravity♪
♪ كيفية مواجهة جاذبيتك ♪
♪Pull away from each dimension♪
ابتعد عن كل بُعد ♪
♪Forget everything before I sink♪
♪ انسى كل شيء قبل أن أغرق
♪Even though I don't know my own whereabouts♪
♪ على الرغم من أنني لا أعرف مكاني ♪
♪How to get rid of your gravity♪
♪ كيف تتخلص من جاذبيتك ♪
♪I'm both fascinated and suffocated♪
♪ أنا مفتون ومختنق على حد سواء
♪The cycle is disturbed and the flight is out of control♪
الدورة مضطربة والرحلة خارجة عن السيطرة
♪Eager to crash on the earth with a shooting star♪
♪ حريصة على الاصطدام على الأرض مع شهاب
♪How to counteract your gravity♪
♪ كيفية مواجهة جاذبيتك ♪
♪Pull away from each dimension♪
ابتعد عن كل بُعد ♪
♪Forget everything before I sink♪
♪ انسى كل شيء قبل أن أغرق
♪Even though I don't know my own whereabouts♪
♪ على الرغم من أنني لا أعرف مكاني ♪
Yan Ning,
يان نينج ،
congratulations on realizing your dream,
مبروك على تحقيق حلمك ،
and having your own concert.
وإقامة الحفلة الموسيقية الخاصة بك.
Mm.
مم.
When your movie hits the big screen,
عندما يظهر فيلمك على الشاشة الكبيرة ،
I'll also grant one of your wishes,
سأوافق أيضًا على إحدى رغباتك ،
whatever it is.
مهما تكن.
Whatever it is, really?
أيا كان حقا؟
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Well,
نحن سوف،
what if I ask you to marry me?
ماذا لو طلبت منك الزواج مني؟
It's a deal.
انها صفقة.
Yeah.
نعم.
♪Put my phone on the left side near my heart♪
♪ ضع هاتفي على الجانب الأيسر بالقرب من قلبي
♪Your voice sounds like a missed call♪
صوتك يبدو وكأنه مكالمة فائتة
♪How to give up and how to erase your memory♪
كيف تستسلم وكيف تمحو ذاكرتك
♪Sometimes near, sometimes far, sometimes the signals connect♪
أحيانًا قريبة ، وأحيانًا بعيدة ، وأحيانًا تتصل الإشارات
♪Your breath sounds more and more clear before dawn♪
أنفاسك تبدو أكثر وضوحًا قبل الفجر
♪The past is scattered all over the place♪
الماضي مبعثر في كل مكان
♪I remained where I was and waited for you♪
♪ بقيت حيث كنت وانتظرتك ♪
♪Doing my one-man show♪
♪ القيام ببرنامجي الفردي ♪
♪The deeper the scar, the more involved I am♪
♪ كلما كانت الندبة أعمق ، كنت أكثر انخراطًا
♪The more I try to forget, the more I miss you♪
♪ كلما حاولت أن أنسى ، اشتقت إليك أكثر
♪Losing you♪
خسارتك ♪
♪I sunk in there myself♪
♪ غرقت هناك بنفسي ♪
♪I crash on an isolated island♪
♪ تحطمت على جزيرة معزولة ♪
♪Covered in scars, I need the antidote, while the rain is pouring♪
مغطاة بالندوب ، أحتاج إلى الترياق ، بينما المطر ينهمر ♪
♪You don't care about the thing I treasure most♪
♪ أنت لا تهتم بالشيء الذي أعتز به أكثر
♪In an instant my heartbeat is frozen♪
♪ في لحظة تجمد دقات قلبي ♪
♪Broken pride♪
كبرياء مكسور
♪Once impulsive, then regretful, does it matter♪
بمجرد الاندفاع ، ثم الندم ، فهل يهم
♪You turn around, leaving me nowhere to go♪
♪ تستدير ، تاركة لي مكانًا أذهب إليه
♪Be your disciple and beg for love♪
♪ كن تلميذك واستجداء الحب ♪
♪Broken pride♪
كبرياء مكسور
♪Once impulsive, then regretful, does it matter♪
بمجرد الاندفاع ، ثم الندم ، فهل يهم
♪You turn around, leaving me nowhere to go♪
♪ تستدير ، تاركة لي مكانًا أذهب إليه
♪Be your disciple and beg for love♪
♪ كن تلميذك واستجداء الحب ♪
=Yan Zhi's Romantic Story=
= قصة رومانسية يان تشي =
(The right of communication through network)
(حق الاتصال عبر الشبكة)
(is exclusively owned by Tencent)
(مملوكة حصريًا لشركة Tencent)